Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- International Offices, 1980-2000 and undated, (80 boxes)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Philippines (Manila)
      - One McKinley Place, 1997 (Box IO-OV5)
      - TA Bank, 1997 (Box IO-OV5)
    - Portugal (Lisbon)
      - Associação Sol, undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - Via Catarina shopping center, undated (Box IO-OV5)
    - Puerto Rico (San Juan)
      - American Express, 1993 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Banco Popular de P.R., 1996 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Frito-Lay/KFC tie-in, 1993-1995 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Kentucky Fried Chicken, undated, (2 folders) (Box IO-OV5)
    - Singapore
      - American Express, 1993, (2 folders) (Box IO-OV5)
      - Ampitheatre at Tiger Balm Gardens, undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - Apple, 1993 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Ikea, undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - Morgan Greenfell Investment Management, undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - Lacoste, undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - Rockport, 1996 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Singapore Post, 1995 (Box IO-OV5)
    - South Africa (Johannesburg)
      - Ford, 1994 (Box IO-OV5)
    - Spain (Barcelona)
      - Casa de Cataluñya, 1997 (Box IO-OV5)
      - Codorniu (Cava), undated (Box IO-OV5)
      - STIM/Citypark, 1993-1994 (Box IO-OV5)
    - Spain (Madrid)
      - Wunderman self-promotion, 1988-1989 (Box IO-OV5)
    - Sweden (Stockholm)
      - Apple, 1990 and undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Esselte Meto, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Kraft, Daim candy bar, 1997 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Philip Morris, 1990-1991 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Pripos (BCP), 1995 (Box IO-OV6)
      - SL (Swedish Rail), 1995, (2 folders) (Box IO-OV6)
      - Telia, 1994-1997 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Wunderman self-promotion, 1990 (Box IO-OV6)
    - Switzerland (Zurich)
      - Milk On Tour, 1993 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Motorola, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Orangina, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Philip Morris, 1992-1993 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Telecom PTT/Cineprix, undated (Box IO-OV6)
    - Thailand (Bangkok)
      - American Express, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Honda, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Kentucky Fried Chicken (article), 1995 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Thai Airways/Royal Orchid Plus, 1995 (Box IO-OV6)
      - UTV, undated (Box IO-OV6)
    - United Kingdom (London)
      - American Airline, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - American Express, 1994-1995 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Ericsson, 1997 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Ford, undated (Box IO-OV6)
      - Novell/Compaq, 1997 (Box IO-OV6)
      - Pepsi, undated (Box IO-OV6)
    - Venezuela (Caracas)
      - Kentucky Fried Chicken/Pepsi, undated (Box IO-OV6)
    - Various Offices
      - Pan-European Case Histories, 1996-1997 (Box IO-OV6)
  - Restricted Files
    - Australia (Adelaide)
      - Citibank/CRY Card (India), 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Brazil (São Paulo)
      - Citibank case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Canada (Toronto)
      - Tetra Pak, 1998, (2 folders) (Box IO-R1)
    - Colombia (Bogota)
      - Citibank status report, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - France (Paris)
      - Bouygues Telecom case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Danone (Box IO-R1)
      - Case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Event marketing, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - CD-ROM marketing toolbox1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Eurotunnel--Horse Guard campaign, 1998-1999 (Box IO-R1)
      - Général des Eaux case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - IBM case history, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Jaguar, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - SCNF case study, 1999 (Box IO-R1)
      - Unilever, Pour Tout Vous Dire, 1999 (Box IO-R1)
    - Italy (Milan)
      - Club la Republica case history, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Hertz Link case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - IBM case history, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Novartis Nutrition, Dietor sweetener case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Rank Xerox, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam)
      - KLM case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Public Service case studies, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Puerto Rico (San Juan)
      - Sony case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Teodoro Moscoso Bridge, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Singapore
      - Citibank Citigold case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Port of Singapore case study, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Spain (Barcelona)
      - Bertelsman Direct, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Cardhu whiskey, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Fira de Barcelona, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Hotel Arts Barcelona, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
      - Jaguar, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
    - Thailand (Bangkok)
      - Fuji film, 1998 (Box IO-R1)
  - International Offices Slides, 1982-1999 and undated
    - Argentina (Buenos Aires) (Box IO-S1)
    - Australia (Adelaide) (Box IO-S1)
    - Australia (Melbourne) (Box IO-S1)
    - Australia (Sydney), (2 folders) (Box IO-S1)
    - Austria (Vienna), (2 folders) (Box IO-S1)
    - Belgium (Brussels), (2 folders) (Box IO-S1)
    - Brazil (São Paulo), (3 folders) (Box IO-S2)
    - Canada (Toronto), (3 folders) (Box IO-S2)
    - Chile (Santiago) (Box IO-S2)
    - China (Hong Kong), (2 folders) (Box IO-S3)
    - Colombia (Bogota) (Box IO-S3)
    - Czech Republic (Prague) (Box IO-S3)
    - Denmark (Copenhagen), (3 folders) (Box IO-S3)
    - Dominican Republic (Santo Domingo) (Box IO-S3)
    - Finland (Helsinki), (2 folders) (Box IO-S4)
    - France (Paris), (6 folders) (Box IO-S4)
    - Germany, (5 folders) (Box IO-S5)
    - Greece (Athens) (Box IO-S5)
    - Guatemala (Guatemala City) (Box IO-S5)
    - Hungary (Budapest) (Box IO-S5)
    - India (Madras) (Box IO-S6)
    - Ireland (Box IO-S6)
    - Italy (Milan and Rome), (4 folders) (Box IO-S6)
    - Japan (Tokyo), (2 folders) (Box IO-S6)
    - Malaysia (Kuala Lumpur), (2 folders) (Box IO-S7)
    - Mexico (Mexico City), (2 folders) (Box IO-S7)
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam), (3 folders) (Box IO-S7)
    - New Zealand (Auckland) (Box IO-S7)
    - Norway (Oslo), (2 folders) (Box IO-S7)
    - Philippines (Manila) (Box IO-S8)
    - Portugal (Lisbon), (2 folders) (Box IO-S8)
    - Puerto Rico (San Juan), (2 folders) (Box IO-S8)
    - Singapore (Box IO-S8)
    - South Africa (Johannesburg), (2 folders) (Box IO-S8)
    - Spain (Barcelona and Madrid), (3 folders) (Box IO-S8)
    - Sweden (Stockholm), (2 folders) (Box IO-S9)
    - Switzerland (Zurich) (Box IO-S9)
    - Taiwan (Box IO-S9)
    - Thailand (Bangkok) (Box IO-S9)
    - United Kingdom (London, Essex, Byfleet, Woking), (1-3 of 7 folders) (Box IO-S9)
    - United Kingdom (London, Essex, Byfleet, Woking) (continued), (4-7 of 7 folders) (Box IO-S10)
    - Uruguay (Montevideo) (Box IO-S10)
    - Venezuela (Caracas) (Box IO-S10)
    - Zimbabwe (Harare) (Box IO-S10)
    - International and domestic slides, 1995 (Box IO-S10)
    - International Managers' Meeting, 1995 (Box IO-S10)
    - International Symposium, 1980, (2 folders) (Box IO-S11)
    - Miscellaneious international creative, 1995-1996 and undated, (4 folders) (Box IO-S11)
  - Three-Dimensional Materials
    - Australia (Adelaide)
      - Adelaide Convention and Tourist Authority, laptop package, undated (Box IO-T1)
      - Orlando Wyndham/Havana Club, t-shirt and shot glass, undated (Box IO-T1)
    - Australia (Melbourne)
      - Autofleet, box with wrench, 1990 (Box IO-T1)
      - DuPont Corian, 1990 (Box IO-T1)
      - Powercor, 1996 (Box IO-T1)
      - Redbook Performance Plus, 1994 (Box IO-T1)
    - Australia (Sydney)
      - Colgate oral care mailer, 1990 (Box IO-T1)
    - Austria (Vienna)
      - Victorinox, compass in wooden box, undated (Box IO-T1)
    - Brazil (São Paulo)
      - Colgate, undated (Box IO-T2)
      - Cultura Artistica, 1993 (Box IO-T2)
      - National Bank, Banquinho Turma de Mõnica, undated (Box IO-T2)
    - Canada (Toronto)
      - American Express, Platinum Card membership kit (small binder), undated (Box IO-T2)
      - Ford, The Plan Action Center, 1994 (Box IO-T2)
    - Chile (Santiago)
      - Transbank, juice squeezer, undated (Box IO-T2)
    - China (Hong Kong)
      - Mercedes Benz, 1991 (Box IO-T2)
    - Colombia (Bogota)
      - Citibank Paytm, 1998 (Box IO-T2)
    - Czech Republic (Prague)
      - Bond Street cigarettes (Philip Morris), point-of-purchase displays, 1994-1997 (Box IO-T3)
    - Denmark (Copenhagen)
      - Ford, mailing tube, undated (Box IO-T3)
      - Institut for Kostanalyse (Voksen), undated (Box IO-T3)
    - Finland (Helsinki)
      - Scan (cured meats), styrofoam display, 1995 (Box IO-T3)
      - Ulrika Charlotan, undated (Box IO-T3)
    - France (Paris)
      - Wunderman Lacroix self-promotion, undated (Box IO-T3)
    - Germany
      - Eternit, package with rock, 1996 (Box IO-T4)
    - Germany (Frankfurt)
      - Ford Cougar, 1996, 1998 (Box IO-T4)
      - Ford Ka, For Your Eyes Only, 1996 (Box IO-T4)
      - Ford, PKW-Verkaufshandbuch, 1996 (Box IO-T4)
      - Ford Scorpio, Kunden-Bildungs Programme, 1991 (Box IO-T4)
      - Hugo Boss, undated (Box IO-T4)
      - Jaguar Owners Club, undated (Box IO-T5)
      - Kaffe Hag, undated (Box IO-T5)
    - Germany (Cologne)
      - Simrit/Freudenberg catalog mailer, 1991 (Box IO-T5)
    - Guatemala (Guatemala City)
      - Glidden Club del Pintor, La Paleta, paint can mailing, 1996 (Box IO-T5)
    - Italy (Milan)
      - BMW 5 Series, 1992 (Box IO-T5)
      - BMW Marketing Vetture d'Occasione, 1991 (Box IO-T6)
      - Bticino, 1996 (Box IO-T6)
      - INA Assitalia Services, Duemila campaign kit, 1997 (Box IO-T6)
      - INA Assitalia Services, Una Family campaign kit, 1997 (Box IO-T6)
    - Japan (Tokyo)
      - American Express Platinum Card welcome kit, wallet and luggage tags, 1993 (Box IO-T6)
      - IBM, 1995 (Box IO-T6)
      - IBM, model 3380 promotion with golf balls, undated (Box IO-T7)
      - ITJ (International Telecom Japan), Valentine gift box with chocolate and tea, undated (Box IO-T7)
      - Yamaco mailer, undated (Box IO-T7)
    - Mexico (Mexico City)
      - Ford, Grand Marquis, 1998 (Box IO-T7)
      - Lincoln Continental, 1997 (Box IO-T7)
      - Lincoln Town Car, 1997 (Box IO-T7)
      - Moët et Chandon, Dom Perignon rosé, undated (1989 or 1995) (Box IO-T7)
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam)
      - PTT Telecom, 1993 (Box IO-T8)
    - New Zealand (Auckland)
      - Air New Zealand, luggage tags, undated (Box IO-T8)
    - Portugal (Lisbon)
      - British Airways, package with tea cup, undated (Box IO-T8)
      - GALP/Petrogal, circa 1994 (Box IO-T8)
      - GALP Energia (Petrogal), package with soccer ball, undated (Box IO-T8)
      - Grupo Brodheim, 1997 (Box IO-T8)
      - Motorola pager, with VHS case for Home Alone movie, circa 1993 (Box IO-T9)
      - Petrogal, circa 1994 (Box IO-T9)
    - Spain (Barcelona)
      - Caja España, 1994 (Box IO-T9)
      - Informat, 2 mailers, 1998 (Box IO-T9)
      - Jaguar, package with keychain, 1998 (Box IO-T9)
    - Spain (Madrid)
      - Knockando Scotch, undated (Box IO-T9)
      - Monsanto RoundUp, 1995 (Box IO-T10)
      - Sony demonstration stand, undated (Box IO-T10)
    - Sweden (Stockholm)
      - Apple Powerbook, 1992 (Box IO-T10)
      - Telia, 1996 (Box IO-T10)
      - Thailand (Bangkok) (Box IO-T11)
      - Wunderman self-promotion, package with nail puzzle, 1995 (Box IO-T11)
    - United Kingdom
      - American Express, partnership with Lloyd's Bank, 1991 (Box IO-T11)
      - British Telecom, file box, undated (Box IO-T11)
      - Ericsson, Dealer Support Manual, 1997 (Box IO-T11)
      - Ford mailer, 1997 (Box IO-T11)
      - Ford Cares, leather binder, 1997 (Box IO-T11)
      - Ford Cares mailing, undated (Box IO-T11)
      - Ford Customer Connection, 1996 (Box IO-T12)
      - Ford, Look Inside To Drive Your Business, Amateur golf tournament, package with golf ball, 1996 (Box IO-T12)
      - Ford Probe Dealer Prospect Kit, 1994 (Box IO-T12)
      - Ford Probe Marketing Guide, 1994 (Box IO-T12)
      - Ford RS Cosworth mailers, 1991 (Box IO-T12)
      - Guardian Insurance, ReLease, 1996 (Box IO-T13)
      - Kentucky Fried Chicken/Pepsi, hat, undated (Box IO-T13)
    - Venezuela (Caracas)
      - Aruba Sonesta resorts, t-shirt in zippered bag, 1995 (Box IO-T13)
      - Xerox, pillow, 1996 (Box IO-T13)
    - Unidentified Office
      - Ericsson product stand, undated (Box IO-T13)
      - Ford Galaxy Pan-European launch books, 1995 (Box IO-T14)
      - Ford Mondeo Pan-European launch books, undated (Box IO-T15)
  - Irregular Sized Materials
    - Argentina (Buenos Aires)
      - Guia Ford/Mira binder, 1996 (Box IO-T16)
    - Hungary (Budapest)
      - WCJ Gästebuch, guest book, undated (Box IO-T16)
    - Italy (Milan)
      - Bosch presentation package with clock, circa 1987 (Box IO-T16)
    - Mexico (Mexico City)
      - American Express, Travel Services binder, circa 1992 (Box IO-T16)
    - United Kingdom
      - British Telecom, Power Pack, 1994 (Box IO-T16)
      - Ford, In Business Guide for Fleet Owners, 1997 (Box IO-T16)
    - France (Paris)
      - Cent Ans chefs d'Oeuvre, film tin package with VHS of Gone With The Wind, removed to Audiovisual Materials, undated (Box IO-T17)
      - L'Oreal cosmetic sampler, round wooden package, undated (Box IO-T17)
    - Germany (Frankfurt)
      - SAIA, 1989 (Box IO-T17)
    - Italy (Milan)
      - BMW dealer communications manual, 1994 (Box IO-T17)
    - China (Hong Kong)
      - Wunderman Breakfast, package with cereal box, 1997 (Box IO-T18)
      - Wunderman Breakfast, package with china plate, 1997 (Box IO-T18)
    - Portugal (Lisbon)
      - Colombo Center pop-up book, circa 1994 (Box IO-T19)
- New Business Files, 1959-1999 and undated, (10 boxes)
  Consists of materials relating to Wunderman's efforts to acquire new business and new client relationships. Presentations, campaign and market segment analyses and external research reports are included. Many of the prospective clients have related materials in the Account Files and International Offices Series, once they became actual clients for the agency. Arranged alphabetically by company name.
  - American Express
    - Charge Card analysis, 1959 (Box NB1)
  - AT&T
    - Brand Day meeting, 1984 (Box NB1)
    - Evaluation of Opportunity Calling program (by Information Resources), 1986 (Box NB1)
    - Service line descriptions, undated (Box NB1)
    - World Traveler, 1993, (2 folders) (Box NB1)
  - Atari
    - Video Computer Systems, 1981 (Box NB1)
  - BankCal
    - Presentation, 1981 (Box NB1)
  - Blockbuster Video
    - Presentation, 1993, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box NB1)
    - Presentation, 1993, (3 of 3 folders) (Box NB2)
  - Canon Copier Division
    - Dealer support campaign, 1982 (Box NB2)
  - Cato Johnson
    - Credentials, circa 1977 (Box NB2)
  - CBS, Inc.
    - Executive Summary of Videotex Market Research, 1983 (Box NB2)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's
    - Evaluation of Skin Care Market in the U.K., 1983 (Box NB2)
  - Columbia House
    - Pacific Stereo joint promotion, 1980 (Box NB2)
    - Telephone confirmation proposal, 1979 (Box NB2)
  - Columbia Record and Tape Club
    - Strategy Review Board, 1979 (Box NB2)
  - Consumer Dialog
    - Data Based Personalized Communications System, 1984 (Box NB2)
  - Diner's Club
    - General, 1974-1980, (2 folders) (Box NB2)
    - Exploratory research, 1978 (Box NB3)
    - Presentation, 1978 (Box NB3)
  - Financial Communications Society
    - Presentation, 1981 (Box NB3)
  - Future Industries
    - General, 1989-1991, (7 folders) (Box NB3)
  - GEICO
    - Brief History of Marketing and Advertising, vol. II (Jim Howard), 1980 (Box NB3)
    - Meeting, 1980 (Box NB3)
    - Polaris Research proposal, 1980 (Box NB3)
  - General Foods
    - Emerging Specialty Foods Business, 1983 (Box NB4)
    - Future 1993, undated (Box NB4)
    - Home Chef, 1980 (Box NB4)
    - International Coffees, 1979 (Box NB4)
    - Specialty Foods, 1983 (Box NB4)
    - Specialty Foods Business Review, 1984 (Box NB4)
  - General New Business
    - Reports and miscellaneous, undated, (2 folders) (Box NB4)
  - Geo Magazine
    - Telephone marketing proposal, 1979 (Box NB4)
  - Gino's
    - Columbia Record and Tape Club joint promotion, 1980 (Box NB4)
  - Harlequin Books
    - Presentation, 1976, (2 folders) (Box NB5)
  - Heinz Venture Group
    - General, 1989-1990, (3 folders) (Box NB5)
    - Project 100, 1990 (Box NB5)
    - Response to questionnaire, 1989 (Box NB5)
  - IBM
    - Training proposal, 1986 (Box NB5)
  - J.C. Penney
    - Life Touch Portrait Studio, undated (Box NB5)
  - Kenner Toys
    - Presentation, 1979 (Box NB5)
  - New York City Economic Development Corporation
    - Presentation, 1996 (Box NB6)
  - Sears Home Services
    - Presentation, 1996 (Box NB6)
  - SwissAir
    - Presentation, 1996 (Box NB6)
  - U.S. Mint
    - Bicentennial Constitution Coin program, 1987, (1-3 of 4 folders) (Box NB6)
    - Bicentennial Constitution Coin program, 1987, (4 of 4 folders) (Box NB7)
  - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
    - Case Studies--What We Do, undated (Box NB7)
    - Pitch, undated (Box NB7)
    - Presentation Library, 1992, (2 folders) (Box NB7)
    - WCJ-NY Topline Credentials, undated (Box NB7)
    - WCJ-Sports Action Marketing presentation, 1996 (Box NB7)
    - Worldwide Supplementary Credentials, 1997 (Box NB7)
  - Wunderman International Limited
    - New Business pitch, undated (Box NB8)
  - Wunderman, Ricotta & Kline (WRK)
    - Credentials, undated, (2 folders) (Box NB8)
  - Wunderman Worldwide (WW)
    - Credentials, 1990 and undated, (3 folders) (Box NB8)
    - Credentials Library, 1991 (Box NB8)
  - Y&R Direct Marketing Group
    - Credentials, undated (Box NB8)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Club Disney (Box NB-OV1)
      - Making Magic Together presentation, circa 1997 (Box NB-OV1)
    - Harlequin Books
      - Display designs, 1976 (Box NB-OV1)
    - U.S. Postal Service
      - Eagle 2000 Executive Summary, 1994 (Box NB-OV1)
      - Eagle 2000 Source Selection Committee presentation, 1994 (Box NB-OV1)
      - Eagle 2000 Technical/Management proposal, 1994 (Box NB-OV1)
    - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
      - New Business Pitch (English and German), undated (Box NB-OV1)
  - Restricted Materials
    - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ) (Box NB-R1)
      - Capabilities overview, 1999 (Box NB-R1)
      - Credentials, 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box NB-R1)
- Printed Materials, 1950-2001 and undated, (11 boxes)
  Includes internal and commercial publications: newsletters, corporate reports, trade publications, reports, business educational materials. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Commercial Publications
    - Ad Council--Food is More than Just Something to Eat (Y&R project?), undated (Box PM1)
    - American Association of Advertising Agencies (AAAA)--booklets, 1989-1990 (Box PM1)
      [Includes What Every Account Executive Should Know About Marketing Plans, What Every Account Executive Should Know About Media]
    - American Management Association (AMA) training brochures, 1990 (Box PM1)
    - Australia Post--Concept of Direct Marketing (Vin Jenkins), 1984 (Box PM1)
    - Business Professional Advertising Association (BPAA)--Handbook of Business Direct Mail Advertising, 1983 (Box PM1)
    - Clippings and miscellaneous, 1988-2000 (Box PM1)
    - Direct Marketing Association (DMA)
      - 75th Anniversary, 1992 (Box PM1)
      - DMA Echo Locator, 1991 (Box PM1)
      - Effectiveness of 800 Numbers in Direct Mail Catalogs (Esther Lazaros), 1983 (Box PM1)
    - End of the Road for Ladies' Mile? (Margaret Moore), 1986 (Box PM1)
    - Executive Handbook (Personnel Decisions), 1997 (Box PM1)
    - From Managing to Empowering (Scott Parre, Quality Resources), 1994 (Box PM1)
    - InfoSource, undated (Box PM1)
    - Nilson Report, 1990 (Box PM1)
    - Self-Managing Teams (Rollin Glaser, HRD Quarterly), 1991 (Box PM2)
      [Includes Learning to Be a Self-Managed Team, Helping Your Organization Gear Up for Self Managed Teams, Facilitating Self Managed Teams, Moving Your Team Toward Self-Management]
    - Skillbuilding for Self-Directed Team Members (Ann and Bob Harper, MW Corp.), 1992 (Box PM2)
    - 60 Role Plays for Management and Supervisory Training (David Turner, McGraw-Hill), 1992 (Box PM2)
    - Taking the Mass out of Marketing (Joel Tucciarone, Montreux Direct Marketing Review), 1987 (Box PM2)
    - Team Accountability (Eileen Russon, HRD Quarterly), 1994 (Box PM2)
    - U.S. Postal Service
      - Advertising Age supplement, 1993 (Box PM2)
      - Business Guide to Advertising with Direct Mail, 1996 (Box PM2)
      - Marketing with Mail, miscellaneous reports, undated (Box PM2)
      - Small Business Guide to Advertising with Direct Mail, 1996 (Box PM2)
    - Viewdata and Its Potential Impact in Direct Marketing (Hoke Communications), 1980 (Box PM2)
    - Y&R and Broadcasting (Museum of Broadcasting), undated (Box PM2)
  - Corporate Publications
    - Impiric
      - Marketing Lab, circa 2000 (Box PM3)
    - Lester Wunderman
      - Business to Business Direct Marketing, undated (Box PM3)
      - Frontiers of Direct Marketing, 1980-1993 (Box PM3)
    - Wunderman
      - Avec le Groupe Wunderman, undated (Box PM3)
      - Wunderman on the Move, 1988 (Box PM3)
    - Wunderman Cato Johnson (WCJ)
      - Action magazine, undated (Box PM3)
      - Action Marketing, circa 1994 (Box PM3)
      - Corporate Identity Guidelines, undated (Box PM3)
      - Creative Review Best of Europe, undated (Box PM3)
      - Creative Works, 1998 (Box PM3)
      - Growing Customer Equity, undated (Box PM3)
      - Media Monitor, 1994 (Box PM3)
      - One Voice (glossary of terms), undated (Box PM3)
    - Wunderman Worldwide (WW)
      - A Worldwide Look--Advertising for American Express, 1989 (Box PM4)
      - Analytic Services, 1989 (Box PM4)
      - El Camino Mas Corte Para Crear Negocio, undated (Box PM4)
      - Guide of Marketing in Spain, 1989 (Box PM4)
      - La Wunderman Tender é Traslocata (We Have Moved), undated (Box PM4)
      - Les 4 Verités du Marketing Direct, undated (Box PM4)
      - Making the Message Count, undated (Box PM4)
      - Media Monitor, 1992 (Box PM4)
      - We've Changed Our Name to Reflect What We Really Are, undated (Box PM4)
    - Young & Rubicam (Y&R)
      - Alex Kroll reprints, undated (Box PM4)
        [Includes God Helps Those Who Help Their Customers, Marketing and Business Opportunities in Eastern Europe and the Soviet Union, Remember Brands Are People Too]
      - Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Box PM4)
      - Brand Asset News, 1995 (Box PM4)
      - Facts and Figures, 1990-1995 (Box PM4)
      - Idea, issue 3, 1993 (Box PM4)
      - In Review, circa 1996 (Box PM4)
      - Issues, 1976-1983 (Box PM4)
      - Joseph de Deo, Why Over $228 Billion is Spent on Advertising..., undated (Box PM4)
      - Miscellaneous brochures, 1980s (Box PM4)
      - Our Profile, circa 1998 (Box PM5)
      - Y&R Product Group Owners Manual, undated (Box PM5)
      - Young & Rubicam World, 1977-1985 (Box PM5)
  - Books
    - Benson, Richard. 1987. Secrets of Successful Direct Mail. Benson Organization. (Box PM6)
    - Block and Robinson, eds. 1994. Sales Promotion Handbook, 8th ed. Dartnell. (Box PM6)
    - Dillon, John. 1976. Handbook of International Direct Marketing. McGraw-Hill. (Box PM6)
    - Eicoff, Al. 1988. Eicoff on Broadcast Direct Marketing. NTC. (Box PM6)
    - Emmet and Jeuck. 1950. Catalogues and Counters: A History of Sears, Roebuck and Company. University of Chicago Press. (Box PM6)
    - Gladwell, Malcolm. 2000. The Tipping Point: How Little Things Can Make a Big Difference. Little, Brown. (Box PM6)
    - Jackson, Don. 1989. 151 Secrets of Insurance Direct Marketing Practices. Nopoly. (Box PM6)
    - Matathia and Salzman. 1999. Next: Trends for the Near Future. Overlook. (Box PM6)
    - Nadal, Jack. 1987. Cracking the Global Market. American Management Assocation. (Box PM6)
    - Naisbitt, John. 1982. Megatrends. Warner. (Box PM6)
    - Naisbitt and Aburdene. 1990. Megatrends 2000. Morrow. (Box PM6)
    - Ohmae, Kenichi. 1990. The Borderless World. Harper Business. (Box PM6)
    - Peters, Tom. 1992. Liberation Management. Knopf. (Box PM6)